{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993705362","data":{"timestamp":" 946993705361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993705746","data":{"timestamp":" 946993705746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993706241","data":{"timestamp":" 946993706240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993706595","data":{"timestamp":" 946993706594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993707013","data":{"timestamp":" 946993707011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993707498","data":{"timestamp":" 946993707498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993707733","data":{"timestamp":" 946993707733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993710947","data":{"timestamp":" 946993710942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993710985","data":{"timestamp":" 946993710985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993711712","data":{"timestamp":" 946993711711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712117","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712421","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712637","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993712842","data":{"timestamp":" 946993712841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993713174","data":{"timestamp":" 946993713174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993713410","data":{"timestamp":" 946993713409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993716585","data":{"timestamp":" 946993716585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993716998","data":{"timestamp":" 946993716998"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993719609","data":{"timestamp":" 946993719608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993719823","data":{"timestamp":" 946993719822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993720036","data":{"timestamp":" 946993720036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993723525","data":{"timestamp":" 946993723523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993727314","data":{"timestamp":" 946993727313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993728347","data":{"timestamp":" 946993728346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993731104","data":{"timestamp":" 946993731104"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993731488","data":{"timestamp":" 946993731487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993731983","data":{"timestamp":" 946993731982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993732336","data":{"timestamp":" 946993732336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993732753","data":{"timestamp":" 946993732752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993733237","data":{"timestamp":" 946993733237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993733472","data":{"timestamp":" 946993733472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993736727","data":{"timestamp":" 946993736726"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993736767","data":{"timestamp":" 946993736766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993737493","data":{"timestamp":" 946993737492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993737898","data":{"timestamp":" 946993737897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993738202","data":{"timestamp":" 946993738201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993738422","data":{"timestamp":" 946993738421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993738630","data":{"timestamp":" 946993738629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993738962","data":{"timestamp":" 946993738961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993739197","data":{"timestamp":" 946993739196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993741822","data":{"timestamp":" 946993741820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946993741938","data":{"timestamp":" 946993741938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994066945","data":{"timestamp":" 946994066944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 476aa65d-7bd8-43ba-a651-76a48d7d18f4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994103561","data":{"timestamp":" 946994103561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8622dfad-f7f8-49e1-b05b-2bfdb91859cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994147693","data":{"timestamp":" 946994147693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8622dfad-f7f8-49e1-b05b-2bfdb91859cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994147799","data":{"timestamp":" 946994147799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8622dfad-f7f8-49e1-b05b-2bfdb91859cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994188806","data":{"timestamp":" 946994188805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8622dfad-f7f8-49e1-b05b-2bfdb91859cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994209739","data":{"timestamp":" 946994209739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 90f40642-7bc3-4da4-85d1-88c6d6cb1243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994264837","data":{"timestamp":" 946994264836"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 90f40642-7bc3-4da4-85d1-88c6d6cb1243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994264948","data":{"timestamp":" 946994264948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 90f40642-7bc3-4da4-85d1-88c6d6cb1243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994371365","data":{"timestamp":" 946994371364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 90f40642-7bc3-4da4-85d1-88c6d6cb1243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994414555","data":{"timestamp":" 946994414554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994422707","data":{"timestamp":" 946994422706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" START_SIKIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994426469","data":{"timestamp":" 946994426468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994428089","data":{"timestamp":" 946994428088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994436246","data":{"timestamp":" 946994436245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994437868","data":{"timestamp":" 946994437867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994445033","data":{"timestamp":" 946994445033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994446647","data":{"timestamp":" 946994446647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994453309","data":{"timestamp":" 946994453308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994454934","data":{"timestamp":" 946994454933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994458482","data":{"timestamp":" 946994458482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994460092","data":{"timestamp":" 946994460092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994465781","data":{"timestamp":" 946994465781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994467395","data":{"timestamp":" 946994467395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994471836","data":{"timestamp":" 946994471835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994473459","data":{"timestamp":" 946994473458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994479337","data":{"timestamp":" 946994479336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" START_SAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994480389","data":{"timestamp":" 946994480389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994482038","data":{"timestamp":" 946994482037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994484869","data":{"timestamp":" 946994484868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994486475","data":{"timestamp":" 946994486474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994490216","data":{"timestamp":" 946994490216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994491841","data":{"timestamp":" 946994491841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994495684","data":{"timestamp":" 946994495684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994497711","data":{"timestamp":" 946994497709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994497823","data":{"timestamp":" 946994497823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 59070a5d-ef6b-4ce9-9a3c-6e5ed388f041"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994519265","data":{"timestamp":" 946994519265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994523793","data":{"timestamp":" 946994523792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994525416","data":{"timestamp":" 946994525416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994530275","data":{"timestamp":" 946994530274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sabuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994531884","data":{"timestamp":" 946994531883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994535950","data":{"timestamp":" 946994535950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" START_SAHANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994539673","data":{"timestamp":" 946994539673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sahani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994541260","data":{"timestamp":" 946994541259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994547780","data":{"timestamp":" 946994547779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sungura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994549409","data":{"timestamp":" 946994549409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994552283","data":{"timestamp":" 946994552282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994553877","data":{"timestamp":" 946994553877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994564578","data":{"timestamp":" 946994564578"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" START_SUFURIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994566944","data":{"timestamp":" 946994566944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sufuria"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994568586","data":{"timestamp":" 946994568585"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994572422","data":{"timestamp":" 946994572421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994574036","data":{"timestamp":" 946994574035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994576447","data":{"timestamp":" 946994576446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994578059","data":{"timestamp":" 946994578058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994580676","data":{"timestamp":" 946994580675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" swala"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994582297","data":{"timestamp":" 946994582296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994587339","data":{"timestamp":" 946994587338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994588948","data":{"timestamp":" 946994588948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994595582","data":{"timestamp":" 946994595582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994597605","data":{"timestamp":" 946994597603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994597735","data":{"timestamp":" 946994597735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b268a5dd-3cb9-449b-b528-f7aa092e0c55"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994672316","data":{"timestamp":" 946994672316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-u-r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994701430","data":{"timestamp":" 946994701429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_g-w-s"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994722321","data":{"timestamp":" 946994722321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-g-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994731838","data":{"timestamp":" 946994731838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-w-p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994761398","data":{"timestamp":" 946994761397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_h-s-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994764906","data":{"timestamp":" 946994764905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_f-a-s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994770133","data":{"timestamp":" 946994770133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_y-e-s"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994777555","data":{"timestamp":" 946994777555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_y-e-s"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994803215","data":{"timestamp":" 946994803215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_ch-u-s"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994812573","data":{"timestamp":" 946994812573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_s-a-t"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994849430","data":{"timestamp":" 946994849430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_z-w-s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994855197","data":{"timestamp":" 946994855196"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 8d55d036-28c7-472a-8910-7f8f26dca552"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.112"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_s_z-w-s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994906389","data":{"timestamp":" 946994906388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_h_s"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994913002","data":{"timestamp":" 946994913002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_s_l"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994919655","data":{"timestamp":" 946994919655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_l_g"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994926333","data":{"timestamp":" 946994926332"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_s_n"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994933007","data":{"timestamp":" 946994933007"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_i_z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994939670","data":{"timestamp":" 946994939669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_i_s"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994946309","data":{"timestamp":" 946994946309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_w_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994953769","data":{"timestamp":" 946994953769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_w_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994960405","data":{"timestamp":" 946994960404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_s_l"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994967061","data":{"timestamp":" 946994967061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_d_s"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994973736","data":{"timestamp":" 946994973735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_t_o_s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946994985814","data":{"timestamp":" 946994985813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" b1bbcba7-7994-461d-9d2e-a9e761a326a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_t_o_s"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995000650","data":{"timestamp":" 946995000649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 6f4ad1fc-3de2-4340-b919-0c1f4b337aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995004636","data":{"timestamp":" 946995004635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 6f4ad1fc-3de2-4340-b919-0c1f4b337aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995004857","data":{"timestamp":" 946995004857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 6f4ad1fc-3de2-4340-b919-0c1f4b337aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995028581","data":{"timestamp":" 946995028581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" START_A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995029780","data":{"timestamp":" 946995029779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995030842","data":{"timestamp":" 946995030841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995036487","data":{"timestamp":" 946995036487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995037558","data":{"timestamp":" 946995037558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995040206","data":{"timestamp":" 946995040205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995041265","data":{"timestamp":" 946995041264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995044015","data":{"timestamp":" 946995044015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995045070","data":{"timestamp":" 946995045070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995048469","data":{"timestamp":" 946995048468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995049531","data":{"timestamp":" 946995049531"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995052456","data":{"timestamp":" 946995052455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995053512","data":{"timestamp":" 946995053511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995057393","data":{"timestamp":" 946995057393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995058444","data":{"timestamp":" 946995058444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995093934","data":{"timestamp":" 946995093933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995094988","data":{"timestamp":" 946995094987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995098115","data":{"timestamp":" 946995098115"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995099182","data":{"timestamp":" 946995099181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995102409","data":{"timestamp":" 946995102408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995103456","data":{"timestamp":" 946995103456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995107497","data":{"timestamp":" 946995107496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995108548","data":{"timestamp":" 946995108548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995111382","data":{"timestamp":" 946995111381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995112451","data":{"timestamp":" 946995112451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995115315","data":{"timestamp":" 946995115314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995116369","data":{"timestamp":" 946995116369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995118958","data":{"timestamp":" 946995118957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995120023","data":{"timestamp":" 946995120023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995124145","data":{"timestamp":" 946995124145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995125194","data":{"timestamp":" 946995125193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995130513","data":{"timestamp":" 946995130513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995131561","data":{"timestamp":" 946995131561"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995135524","data":{"timestamp":" 946995135523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995136589","data":{"timestamp":" 946995136588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995142699","data":{"timestamp":" 946995142698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995143761","data":{"timestamp":" 946995143760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995147498","data":{"timestamp":" 946995147497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995148560","data":{"timestamp":" 946995148560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995151507","data":{"timestamp":" 946995151506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995152567","data":{"timestamp":" 946995152567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995155939","data":{"timestamp":" 946995155938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995156994","data":{"timestamp":" 946995156994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995159640","data":{"timestamp":" 946995159639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995160697","data":{"timestamp":" 946995160696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995164572","data":{"timestamp":" 946995164571"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" START_Y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995165803","data":{"timestamp":" 946995165802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995166858","data":{"timestamp":" 946995166857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995173381","data":{"timestamp":" 946995173380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995174468","data":{"timestamp":" 946995174468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995177919","data":{"timestamp":" 946995177917"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995178034","data":{"timestamp":" 946995178034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 77817807-a798-4aa1-9fe0-5241d805a23b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946995208126","data":{"timestamp":" 946995208126"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_164809"," gameId":" 04db52a3-2c38-4ab5-afa7-3096ce5f559a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}